<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Online &#8211; Helpdesk Psnet Ucla</title>
	<atom:link href="https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/tag/online/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 16:28:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Explore history by playing video games</title>
		<link>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/explore-history-by-playing-video-games/</link>
					<comments>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/explore-history-by-playing-video-games/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 16:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Featured Posts]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Games]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[history]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Online]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[video]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/?p=848</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Once upon a time, &#8216;mentors&#8217; would turn their noses up when they heard the word video game. There was an uproar saying &#8216;young society is excited&#8217;. However, the picture has not completely changed yet. However, the outlook towards video games has been somewhat positive. There is a lot to learn from video games! If you [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p><span>Once upon a time, &#8216;mentors&#8217; would turn their noses up when they heard the word video game. There was an uproar saying &#8216;young society is excited&#8217;. However, the picture has not completely changed yet. However, the outlook towards video games has been somewhat positive. There is a lot to learn from video games! If you can&#8217;t embrace the material of time, can&#8217;t practice its good aspects, then you have to go on for the rest of your life saying &#8216;what a beautiful day I had before&#8217;.</span></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>Video games are one of the most interesting inventions of the time, one of the main sources of entertainment for children. Of course, video game &#8216;players&#8217; can no longer be confined to a certain age. People of all ages are getting interested in games lately. Video games have overtaken entertainment media such as music and movies in popularity and economic importance. The Game Awards 2022, organized to recognize the best video games of the year, was watched live by more than 100 million viewers. The game&#8217;s artistic value and cultural significance are less discussed than its success as an entertainment medium. Here are some examples of games that can enrich our history and cultural awareness.</p>
<p>&#8216;Heroes of 71&#8217; is the first video game made on the liberation war. This game was released on Google Play Store on December 16, 2015. In this game, the fictional guerilla group Shamsu Bahini has to use weapons against the Pakistani forces in various stages of the great war of independence. Through this, the youth are getting acquainted with the background, horror, importance and partial warfare of the liberation war. Youngsters feel an authentic sense of the spirit of the 1970s when the protagonist throws grenades at the Pakistani soldiers proclaiming Jai Bangla. After the huge success of &#8216;Heroes of 71&#8217;, &#8216;Portbliss Games&#8217; released two more episodes on Play Store &#8211; &#8216;Heroes of 71: Retaliation&#8217; and &#8216;Liberation Camp&#8217;.</p>
<p>&#8216;Age of Empire&#8217; is another historical based war game. It was first released in 1997. At the beginning of the game you have to choose a civilization from the history page. After entering the preparatory period of that civilization, a few workers must be employed to collect wood, stone, food, etc. and establish a settlement. By gradually inventing armies, buildings and fleets you will advance to the next level of civilization. In this way you can build civilizations from the Stone Age to the Renaissance. At the same time, you can learn about the variety of architecture, weapons, tools, clothing, military customs, governance system used at that time. From the first to the fifth season of this game, you can get to know about 40 civilizations including Vikings, Romans, Japanese, Mongolians.</p>
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p><span>The American West of the late 19th century, where the rule of law was weak, is the backdrop for the play Red Dead Redemption. This area was then called the Wild West. Through this play we get a clear and unbiased picture of the superstitions of the people of that time, the men&#8217;s view of women, the life of the cowboys and the oppression of the Native Americans. In addition, the enormous popularity and effectiveness of Pinkerton&#8217;s private intelligence forces compared to the US military and law enforcement agencies at the time is educationally highlighted.</span></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p><span>Apart from this, there is a lot to learn about history and civilization from the Second World War-focused Call of Duty and Battlefield game series, &#8216;Kingdom Come: Deliverance&#8217; based on the Middle Ages. By playing these games you can get closer to history than reading books. Because, when you are playing the game, you are no longer in the present, you are part of that time. It&#8217;s like traveling back in time by time travel is an amazing thing!</span></p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/explore-history-by-playing-video-games/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
