<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>United States &#8211; Helpdesk Psnet Ucla</title>
	<atom:link href="https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/tag/united-states/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 17:40:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Helpdesk.png</url>
	<title>United States &#8211; Helpdesk Psnet Ucla</title>
	<link>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Laid-off OpenAI CEO Sam is joining Microsoft</title>
		<link>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/laid-off-openai-ceo-sam-is-joining-microsoft/</link>
					<comments>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/laid-off-openai-ceo-sam-is-joining-microsoft/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wedater]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 17:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[chatgpt]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Microsoft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[North America]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/?p=14</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sam Altman, CEO of OpenAI, the inventor of ChatGPT, is now joining Microsoft. Greg Brockman, the recently resigned president of OpenAI, will work with him at the giant technology company. Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella said this information in a statement. On the other hand, OpenAI has appointed Emmett Scheer as the new CEO. He is ... <a title="Laid-off OpenAI CEO Sam is joining Microsoft" class="read-more" href="https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/laid-off-openai-ceo-sam-is-joining-microsoft/" aria-label="More on Laid-off OpenAI CEO Sam is joining Microsoft">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Sam Altman, CEO of OpenAI, the inventor of ChatGPT, is now joining Microsoft. Greg Brockman, the recently resigned president of OpenAI, will work with him at the giant technology company.</p>



<p>Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella said this information in a statement.</p>



<p>On the other hand, OpenAI has appointed Emmett Scheer as the new CEO. He is the former head of American TV broadcaster TWICE. The news of Sam and Greg joining Microsoft was announced shortly after OpenAI announced the company&#8217;s new CEO.</p>



<p>In a statement, Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella said, &#8216;I am very pleased to announce that Sam Altman and Greg Brockman are joining Microsoft. He will lead a cutting edge artificial intelligence (AI) research team at Microsoft.&#8217;</p>



<p>Satya Nadella also said, Microsoft will provide what they (Sam and Greg) need to succeed.</p>



<p>US technology firm OpenAI&#8217;s board of directors announced the firing of Sam Altman last Friday. The reason given was the board&#8217;s lack of confidence in Sam&#8217;s ability to manage the organization.</p>



<p>Sam, 38, co-founded OpenAI. Greg Brockman announced his resignation as president of OpenAI after the board of directors fired him. He was also the co-founder of the company. Following Sam&#8217;s firing, several key senior executives, including Brockman, left OpenAI.</p>



<p>On November 19, Sam and Greg went to OperaAI headquarters in San Francisco, USA. They went there on the invitation of the company&#8217;s interim CEO Meera Murati. Rumor has it, they are returning to OpenAI.</p>



<p>A year ago, Sam Altman started the big race with artificial intelligence (AI) in the tech world by launching ChatGPT. After that, giant tech companies like Meta, Microsoft, Google and Amazon have invested billions of dollars in the development of artificial intelligence.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/laid-off-openai-ceo-sam-is-joining-microsoft/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
