<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>University of Oxford &#8211; Helpdesk Psnet Ucla</title>
	<atom:link href="https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/tag/university-of-oxford/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 17:34:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/Helpdesk.png</url>
	<title>University of Oxford &#8211; Helpdesk Psnet Ucla</title>
	<link>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Artificial intelligence will predict heart disease</title>
		<link>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/artificial-intelligence-will-predict-heart-disease/</link>
					<comments>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/artificial-intelligence-will-predict-heart-disease/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[wedater]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 17:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Health hazard]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[heart disease]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[treatment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UK]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[University of Oxford]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/?p=11</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) has appeared with the potential to change human life unimaginably. Along with the positives, it also has its negative aspects. However, a recent study has indicated that some unprecedented changes are coming in the use of AI in the medical field. The study was conducted at Oxford University in the UK. Research ... <a title="Artificial intelligence will predict heart disease" class="read-more" href="https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/artificial-intelligence-will-predict-heart-disease/" aria-label="More on Artificial intelligence will predict heart disease">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Artificial intelligence (AI) has appeared with the potential to change human life unimaginably. Along with the positives, it also has its negative aspects. However, a recent study has indicated that some unprecedented changes are coming in the use of AI in the medical field.</p>



<p>The study was conducted at Oxford University in the UK. Research has shown that it is possible to predict whether a person will suffer from heart disease in the future or not, using artificial intelligence. Researchers say that it is possible to get a forecast 10 years in advance, not days-months.</p>



<p>Professor Karalambos Antoniades of Oxford University led the study. This study was conducted on 40,000 people in 8 hospitals in the UK. The researchers closely observed their physical condition for about three years and analyzed the related data.</p>



<p>Through this, researchers have found that those whose blood vessels in the heart are narrowing are at greater risk of serious heart disease and death. Compared to this, twice as many people whose blood vessels in the heart are not narrowed are also at risk of dying from a heart attack or heart disease.</p>



<p>The research team used a new AI tool. Through this, how much fat has accumulated around the blood vessels of a person&#8217;s heart or how quickly the condition is changing, the information is available. At the same time, it is possible to review the risk related to the degree of narrowing of the arteries.</p>



<p>The study, funded by the British Heart Foundation (BHF), says there are millions of people who suffer from chest pain. It is not known whether they are at risk of heart attack or not. You can&#8217;t take treatment or steps to reduce the risk for this. It is possible to know the risk of heart attack in these people using artificial intelligence. It will save thousands of lives from heart disease.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://helpdesk.psnet.ucla.edu/artificial-intelligence-will-predict-heart-disease/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
